3d-savers.com 2015-12-27

# 3D-Savers.com - Privacy Policy

|    
|  |  |  |  |   |  |  |  |  |   |  |  |  |  |   |  |  |  |  |   |  |  |  |  |   |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

|  Privacy Policy   
---  
3D Savers  
3D Savers takes your privacy as seriously as you do. We understand that you want to control your personal information, whether it concerns demographics or preferences. 3D Savers is committed to the responsible management of consumer information and abides by all rules, both ethical and legal, with respect to the use of consumer information. We strictly adhere to all established industry guidelines, and are continuously monitoring and enhancing how we manage the use and security of your personal information to uphold your rights. 3D Savers's Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest quality of service with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our users. This statement will be continually assessed against new technologies and business practices.  
The Use of Information  
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.   
We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.   
We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your electronic referrals. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.   
We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. Agents and contractors of 3D Savers who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for 3D Savers. 3D Savers will not disclose personally identifiable information to companies not owned by us who want to market products or services to you without your prior permission.   
3D-Savers.com contains links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.   
3D Savers may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third-parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons and clear gifs).  
Security  
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.  
Contact Us  
If you have any questions or concerns about this 3D Savers Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via e-mail at the following address: [3dsavers@gmail.com](mailto:3dsavers@gmail.com)  

---  
|    
[](http://www.favdownloads.com/download/Screensavers/Living-3D-Dolphins-Screensaver/?&a=6965&f=3ds_foot2) |  Swim to the ocean depths with Living 3D Dolphins. The beautiful coral seascape is a perfect setting for our amazing 3D dolphins and exotic fish. The sunlight shimmers through the water as the dolphins and fish swim gracefully. The scene comes alive with the sounds of the ocean and dolphins. Truly mesmerizing. 

|   

|  |   
|   
---  
|  | Free Screensavers |   
---|---|---  
| 

**17.05.2010.**   Free 3D Windmill Screensaver - Gorgeous traditional Dutch windmill **more**

**08.02.2010.**   Around the World: Beijing - The Great Wall of China on your desktop! **more**

**06.05.2009.**   Free 3D Japan Screensaver has been released. **more**

**23.03.2009.**   Free Underwater Life Screensaver added to our collection! **more**

**24.01.2009.**   Free Hogwarts Screensaver has come out! **more**

|   
|  |   
  
##### Subscribe to our newsletter:
